Hell of a night
Burn is a thriller, crime, action film directed by Mike Gan.
Lonely, unstable gas station attendant Melinda is tired of being
overshadowed by her more confident, outgoing co-worker Sheila.
When the gas station is held up at gunpoint by Billy, a desperate man in need of quick cash, Melinda
finds an opportunity to make a connection with the robber, regardless of who gets hurt.
Melinda, played by Tilda Cobham-Hervey.
Billy, played by Josh Hutcherson.
Sheila, played by Suki Waterhouse.
Perry, played by Shiloh Fernandez.
Officer Liu, played by Harry Shum Jr..
Dominik, played by James Devoti.
Burn is a 2019 American comedy crime thriller film
written and directed by Mike Gan.
It stars Tilda Cobham-Hervey, Suki Waterhouse, Harry Shum
Jr., Shiloh Fernandez and Josh Hutcherson.
It was released on August 23, 2019, by Momentum
Pictures to mixed or average reviews.
The film explores themes of robbery, gas station,
manipulation, loneliness, attempted rape.
The tone is intense.